https://ferretassn.org/privacy-policy

About UsMissionPolicy StatementPeopleHistoryFinancial ReportsShelter StatisticsShelterAdoptionAdoption ProcessAdoption ApplicationFoster Program DetailsSurrendersAdmission ProcessAssisted AdoptionsLost – FoundACO – Humane OrganizationsACO Guide to FerretsAbout FerretsBehaviorBitingLitter BoxTail WaggingGeneral CareFoodSafe Food HandlingGood Ferret FoodSupplemental FeedingHousingHealthEmergenciesIllness & DiseaseLossRoutine CareVaccinationsCanine Distemper VaccinationRabies VaccinationTips & SuggestionsTreatmentsSafetyBacitracin and FerretsDisaster PreparationHeat & FerretsHoliday Decorating With FerretsPaper Shredder DangerProgramsFoster ProgramNewsletters & BrochuresBrochuresAnimal Control Officer TrainingCanine Distemper Fund – Xavier GroupFerret Care GrantsFerret Shelters DirectorySocial Media ProgramFerret Shelter Forum 2016Workshop VideosGet InvolvedDonateEventsFoster ProgramMembershipShop & SearchVolunteerHelp Ferrets In Your CommunitySocial MediaBlogFacebook PostsTwitter PostsShelter ListingsLibraryArt & HistoryFun & HumorLaw & RegulationsOther MustelidsPaw Print e-News Back IssuesPress ReleasesResources and LinksShelter StoriesA Tale of Two FerretsMiraSitemapShop Our StoreStoreJewelryBeddingClothesFACT ProgramsOther Gifts: Figurines, Household, OrnamentsPatchesToys & PlushCD Fund ItemsShipping Returns & PaymentsAbout Ferret TreasuresHome » Privacy PolicyPrivacy PolicyYour privacy is important to the Ferret Association of Connecticut, Inc (aka FACT).  This privacy statement provides information about the personal information that FACT collects and the ways in which FACT uses that information.We will not sell or disclose any information that identifies you to a third party without your prior approval.We will not send you any email or notify you about new services or special offers unless 1) you register for our e-news mailing list; 2) you make a donation or 3) you make a purchase. You will always be given the opportunity to Unsubscribe from future e-mail communications.We will not sell, trade or rent your personal information to others.For any other questions about our policy, please contact us.Personal Information CollectionThe Ferret Association of Connecticut, Inc (aka FACT) may collect and use the following kinds of personal information:Non-personalized information about your use of this website (including number of visits, referring website);Information that you provide using for the purpose of registering with the websiteAny information that you provide for the purpose of subscribing to the website services; andAny other information that you send to FACT.Using Personal InformationThe Ferret Association of Connecticut, Inc (aka FACT) may use your personal information to:Administer this website;Personalize the website for you;Enable your access to and use of the website services;Publish information about you on the website;Supply to you services that you may choose to purchase;Send to you renewal reminders, statements and invoices;Collect any payments from you; andSend you marketing or other communications regarding this website or respond to your inquires.Where the Ferret Association of Connecticut, Inc (aka FACT) discloses your personal information to its agents or sub-contractors for these purposes, the agent or sub-contractor in question will be obligated to use that personal information in accordance with the terms of this privacy statement.In addition to the disclosures reasonably necessary for the purposes identified elsewhere above, FACT may disclose your personal information to the extent that it is required to do so by law, in connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings, and in order to establish, exercise or defend its legal rights.Securing Your DataThe Ferret Association of Connecticut, Inc (aka FACT) will take reasonable technical and organizational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information.The Ferret Association of Connecticut, Inc (aka FACT) will store all the personal information you provide on its secure servers.Information relating to electronic transactions entered into via this website will be protected by encryption technology.Cross-border Data TransfersInformation that the Ferret Association of Connecticut, Inc (aka FACT) collects may be stored and processed in and transferred between any of the countries in which FACT operates to enable the use of the information in accordance with this privacy policy.In addition, personal information that you submit for publication on the website will be published on the internet and may be available around the world.You agree to such cross-border transfers of personal information.Updating This StatementThe Ferret Association of Connecticut, Inc (aka FACT) may update this privacy policy by posting a new version on this website.You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are familiar with any changes.Other WebsitesThis website contains links to other websites.The Ferret Association of Connecticut, Inc (aka FACT) is not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of any third party.ContactThe Ferret Association of Connecticut, Inc (aka FACT) If you have any questions about this privacy policy or FACT’s treatment of your personal information, please contact us.Credit: This document was created using a Contractology template available at http://www.freenetlaw.com.
Quick Links I Am Looking to Adopt A Ferret I Need to Surrender A Ferret I Lost - Found A Ferret! Ferret Emergencies Ferret Symptoms Chart Ferret Care Brochures FACT Membership Foster A Ferret Volunteer
Blog Contact FACTFACT is approved by the Internal Revenue Service as a 501 (C) (3) tax-exempt organization and all donations are tax deductible to the extent provided by law. FACT's Federal Identification Number (EIN) is 061386567.
Platinum is Guidestar's highest recognition level for publicly disclosing financial and program results.FACT is participant of the Combined Federal Campaign which allows us to accept payroll deductions from federal government and postal employees.
Please use our CFC Code of 40910 to ensure your donations reach us.
